{
  "answers": [
    {
      "answer": "2020",
      "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
      "question_id": "23619426",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Aragon High School",
      "question": "Name of High School",
      "question_id": "23619446",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "answer": "M",
      "question": "Shirt Size",
      "question_id": "23619475",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
      "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
      "question_id": "23619540",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "None",
      "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
      "question_id": "23619629",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "None",
      "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
      "question_id": "23619654",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "None",
      "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
      "question_id": "23619670",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "answer": "I had a great experience last year, and I want to ",
      "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
      "question_id": "23619676",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Some amount",
      "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
      "question_id": "23619742",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "A little bit",
      "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
      "question_id": "23619752",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "A little bit",
      "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
      "question_id": "23619776",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "A lot",
      "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
      "question_id": "23619785",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "I enjoy coding in my free time, especially on the Discord bot I made for my friends. I have attended a few hackathons in the past, but I am still relatively new to the concept. I was also an AP CS A student and was enrolled in Carnegie Mellon's National High School Game Academy for summer 2019.",
      "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
      "question_id": "23619803",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
      "question_id": "23623011",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
      "question_id": "23623088",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is your position there?",
      "question_id": "23623105",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
      "question_id": "23623176",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
      "question_id": "23623194",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
      "question_id": "23623218",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
      "question_id": "23623230",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
      "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
      "question_id": "23675557",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "No",
      "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
      "question_id": "23676865",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Friends | I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
      "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
      "question_id": "23619832",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    {
      "answer": "accepted",
      "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
      "question_id": "23619960",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "answer": "accepted",
      "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
      "question_id": "23620143",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please specify:",
      "question_id": "23619630",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please specify:",
      "question_id": "23619655",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please specify:",
      "question_id": "23675490",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please specify:",
      "question_id": "23619541",
      "type": "text"
    },
    {
      "question": "Please specify:",
      "question_id": "23619833",
      "type": "text"
    }
  ],
  "birth_date": "2002-11-08",
  "changed": "2019-07-13T00:46:05Z",
  "checkedIn": false,
  "created": "2019-07-13T00:46:05Z",
  "email": "yuanp55@gmail.com",
  "event_id": "60509274870",
  "gender": {
    "answer": "Male",
    "question": "What is your gender?",
    "question_id": "23675489",
    "type": "multiple_choice"
  },
  "id": "1255801131",
  "name": "Philip Yuan",
  "onCampus": false,
  "order_id": "981818013",
  "profile": {
    "addresses": {},
    "birth_date": "2002-11-08",
    "cell_phone": "16507853061",
    "email": "yuanp55@gmail.com",
    "first_name": "Philip",
    "last_name": "Yuan",
    "name": "Philip Yuan"
  },
  "quantity": 1,
  "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1255801131/",
  "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
  "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
  "variant_id": null,
  "waiverImage": null,
  "waiverReviewedBy": "",
  "waiverStatus": 0
}